Hey! Hey! Hey!
Quiet!
Put this on.
Hey, why you taking him out?
It's one of theirs. Their traitor.
Hey, we're talking to you.
Get in.
Hurry!
Kneel!
How have you managed
to survive this far, Second Lieutenant?
Is it the guidance…
Of the God you believe in?
You don't deserve to wear this!
Your sin is unforgivable.
You deserve the death penalty!
But the top brass says
you must be executed in our home country.
You…
Will become an example…
In front of thousands of people.
However,
on my ship,
it is my choice how I treat you.
He is one of the captives
who tried to escape last night.
It's too easy to just kill him,
so we will keep this beast alive,
and make him an example like you.
You will come to realize…
Who your true enemy is.
God…
Has abandoned you.
We're under attack
Multiple targets sighted!
We're under attack.
Man the anti-aircraft guns!
Bring someone immediately.
Torpedo!
Piece of shit!
What was that thing?
Did you see it?
Did you see what did this?
What does this…
Dear God, please forgive me.
You're fucking crazy!
Hey. Hey.
Look at me.
If this thing comes back,
we need to be ready for it.
You… you take this,
I keep this.
One doesn't work without the other.
You understand?
Look. Food.
This could come in handy.
Smokes? Do you smoke?
Alright.
More for me then.
Look, coffee.
You drink coffee, right?
I knew this boy.
He was young,
innocent,
tortured for no reason.
You bastards!
Why did you do this to us?
You're animals!
All of you, inhuman!
Sleep well, mate.
Wear this.
It's the same thing.
Not for me, mate.
It'll look better on you.
Have some.
Fuck's sake!
Shit!
Take this.
No, no, it's fine...
Take it.
I'll leave it here.
This is the best damn meal
I've had in a long time.
Almost reminds me of home.
Bronson.
My name.
"Bronson"?
- Yeah.
- Bronson.
Yeah. Near enough.
You?
Saito.
Why are you chained up with me?
Doesn't make us too different, is all.
Yes, finished.
Let's get this chain.
Okay.
Okay, wait.
Wait!
Aim here.
Look carefully.
Right here.
You sure?
It's a bit close, mate.
It's okay.
Aim here.
Okay.
It's okay.
Right here.
Yes.
Now, it's my turn.
Don't worry.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you sure about this?
Fuck it, go on then.
Here we go.
Now you're free.
Yes!
Me and you, we make a good team,
and we can work together on this island.
Bullet. Give me the bullet.
Look at this.
It's the sea creature we saw.
Move!
Come on, get moving!
Walk faster!
Hurry up, faster!
Hide yourself.
Bring this with you.
Bring it.
Trust me.
Wait. Stop.
I smell something.
Check it out.
Don't shoot!
He's one of us!
Are you okay?
How long have you been here?
Since this morning.
Cigarettes!
Are you from the ship?
Yes.
We survived because we wore life jackets.
Everyone else drowned.
Poor bastards.
Fuck!
Hey!
Hand it over.
Water?
No one else is here?
Just you?
Yes.
Before we were attacked,
there was a rumor…
That a traitor was chained up
with an escapee.
Rumors travel quickly on the ship.
Everyone was making bets…
On who would kill who first.
Hey!
Where is he?
Dead.
Drowned.
And you swam
all the way here with his body?
You…
You're not only a traitor,
but a liar, too.
Where is he?
Orang Ikan…
Orang Ikan!
Hey…
Go…
Jesus Christ!
Bronson, let's go.
Saito…
Wait!
Saito!
Hold on!
Saito, wait!
Saito!
Wait!
Saito… Saito!
Saito…
What the fuck are you?
Let's go!
Bronson.
Fuck!
Saito.
Bronson.
You're shaking. Here. This will warm you.
No. Let's go.
That.
Cigarette?
What's in there?
This way.
It's a mermaid.
A mother.
Bronson, it's not safe here. Let's go!
We cannot let this creature live!
Wait!
Killing her child
will only make her more vengeful.
No! Look, it's either us or them!
It's either us…
Or them.
I've got an idea.
Come on, with me.
Come on.
In there. Come on.
Bomb. Look.
Bomb.
In there…
Come on. That's it…
That's it.
Okay. Just here.
That's it. Just here.
Okay.
It's a delayed action fuse…
Christ! It's bent!
We need a tool or something…
Right.
Here.
Bronson…
It's not good! It won't work!
- Bronson…
- No, no, no.
Come on!
Wait, the crash axe.
Yeah, it's in the cockpit.
We could use that!
Yeah, one good hit with that, then…
Four, three, two, one!
- Bronson…
- One of us is going to have to stay…
Here, with the bomb!
Me or you, here!
One of us, here.
My life…
Has carried me to this moment.
We need that axe.
We go together. You cover me.
Go!
Let's do this.
Here, take this.
Come on then, bitch!
Okay, cover me.
Ready, Bronson?
It's working! It's working!
Come on!
It's working!
- I've got it.
- Bronson!
Bronson!
Saito!
Bronson, are you okay?
I'm fucking finished.
Take this!
Take it.
- Get out of here, Saito.
- Bronson!
Go, Saito. Go!
Run, Saito! Run!
Come closer, bitch.
Four…
Three…
Two…
It's okay.
Look carefully.
Aim here.
See you in hell, bitch.
Come on!
Who was Bronson?
Was he a prisoner?
Did he help you?
Were you a prisoner?
Were you on that ship?
On the ship carrying prisoners.
Ask him how he got himself in the brig.
What did you do?
I killed my commanding officer.
I couldn't let my comrades die in vain,
so I killed the man who gave that order.
He killed his commanding officer.
Ask him about this guy, Bronson.
"Bronson"?
Yeah.
Cigarettes?
Do you smoke?
Trust me.
Me and you, we make a good team…
Come on then, bitch!
…and we can work together on this island.
Doesn't make us too different at all.
Bronson!
He was…
My friend.
They were friends.
Is there anyone else on the island?
There's no one else.
Sailors, we're shippin' off home now.
Full speed ahead.